Jessica Graham Web Developer

Jessica Graham

D.O.B 27.06.1991

+64 224716349 hellojessicagraham@gmail.com hellojessica.co

About Me

I began my path to becoming a web developer 10 months ago, some of the skills that I am developing are HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

I have built and published two websites using HTML and CSS which are both responsive and W3C compliant. Also I have experience using Git for version control, and host various projects on <u>Github</u>.

I am constantly continuing to develop my skills as a web developer, whether that be experimenting with projects on <u>codepen</u>, learning new skills for developing websites or keeping up to date with all things industry related.

GitHub: https://github.com/iamjessica

Code Pen: http://codepen.io/hellojessicagraham

Portfolio: www.hellojessica.co

Education

Team Treehouse

- How to make a website
- Introduction to HTML and CSS
- Bootstrap basics
- CSS Layout
- CSS Flexbox Basics
- JavaScript Basics
- JavaScript Loops, Arrays and Objects
- Object-Oriented JavaScript

Books

- HTML and CSS
- JavaScript Programming

Employment History

Head Start Total Body / Colour Technician

MARCH 2017 - PRESENT, AUCKLAND, NEW ZEALAND

- All chemical services and styling
- Managing time effectively
- Assisting stylists
- Basic receptionist duties

The Hair and Beauty Boutique / Colour Director

APRIL 2016 - OCTOBER 2016, SOLIHULL, ENGLAND

- Thoroughly consulting with clients and stylists to deliver colour services that meets clients needs.
- All chemical services and styling
- Educating clients. Prescribing in salon and at home care to ensure correct maintenance of service delivered
- Forming and retaining customer relationships
- Managing time effectively

Tonic Hair and Beauty House / Colour Technician

JANUARY 2015 - APRIL 2016, BRISTOL, ENGLAND

- Thoroughly consulting with clients and stylists to deliver colour services that meets clients needs.
- All chemical services and styling
- Educating clients. Prescribing in salon and at home care to ensure correct maintenance of service delivered
- Forming and retaining customer relationships
- Managing time effectively

Synergy Hair / Colour Director

AUGUST 2015 - OCTOBER 2015, WELLINGTON, NEW ZEALAND

- Thoroughly consulting with clients and stylists to deliver colour services that meets clients needs.
- All chemical services and styling
- Educating clients. Prescribing in salon and at home care to ensure correct maintenance of service delivered
- Forming and retaining customer relationships
- Managing time effectively
- Mentoring apprentices
- Training and presenting new collections to the team

Morgan and Morgan / Senior Colourist

DECEMBER 2014 - JULY 2015, AUCKLAND, NEW ZEALAND

- Thoroughly consulting with clients and stylists to deliver colour services that meets clients needs.
- Educating clients. Prescribing in salon and at home care to ensure correct maintenance of service delivered
- Forming and retaining customer relationships
- Managing time effectively

Referees

I am more than happy to supply referees if requested